THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- CJP Phase I, 1990-2004; 1; 30.4
  - State Interview Summaries, 1991-2004; 1.1; 29.4
    - MO 3060 Johnston *RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - MO 3065-3068 Ebright *RESTRICTED*, 1995; 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - MO 3070-3071 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
    - MO 3073-3076 Ozier*RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
    - NJ 4000-40003 Jackson *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
    - NJ 4004-4006 Loftin *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - NJ 4008-4010 Erozo *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - NJ 4012-4015 Rose *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - NJ 4016-4018 Koedatich *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - NJ 4020-4021 Mayron *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - NJ 4024-4025 Brown *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - NJ 4028 Demarco *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - NJ 4032 Ramseur *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - NJ 4036 Marshall *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - NJ 4040 Bey *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - NJ 4044 Purnell *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - NJ 4048 Mcdouglas *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - NJ 4052 Gerald *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - NJ 4056 Hightower *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - NC 1067-10 Mahaley *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - NC 1071-107 Harris *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - NC1079-1082 Williams *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - NC 1083-108 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - NC 1051-1054 Lemmons *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - NC 1055-1058 Howard *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - NC 1063-106 Jennings*RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - NC 1088-1091 Bishop *RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - NC 1092-1095 Bavis *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - NC 1104 Moss *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - NC 1108-1111 Glenn*RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - NC 1112-1115 Syriani *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - NC 1116 Burr *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - NC 1120-1122 Crotts *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - NC 1124-1126 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - NC 1128-1130 Mosley *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - NC 1132-1134 De Castro *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - NC 1136 Knight *RESTRICTED*, 1993 September (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - NC 1137 Knight *RESTRICTED*, 1993 September (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - NC 1138 Knight *RESTRICTED*, 1993 September (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - NC 1141 R. Lyons *RESTRICTED*, 1994 September (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - NC 1142 R. Lyons *RESTRICTED*, 1994 September (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - NC 1143 R. Lyons *RESTRICTED*, 1994 September (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - NC 1140-1143 Lyons, Robbie james *RESTRICTED*, 2001 October 31; 2004 april (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - NC 1140-1143 Lyons, Robbie james Supplemental Materials *RESTRICTED*, 2004 April (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - NC 1144-1147 Lyons *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - NC 1148-1151 Brogden *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - NC 1152-1155 Brogden*RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - NC 1059-1062 Yelverton *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - NC 1100 Howell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 24 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - PA 0901-0904 Gibson *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - PA 0905-0908 Graziano *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - PA 0909 Pompa *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - PA 0917-0918 Bentacourt *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - PA 0924-0925 Lester *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - PA 0928 Hill *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - PA 0932 Jasper *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - PA 0936-0939 Grier*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - PA 0920-0923, PA 1050 Blount *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - PA 0913-0915 Brown *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - PA 0940 Barrett *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - PA 0944-0947 Brown,K *RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - PA 0948-0951 Santos*RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
    - PA 0950-0975 Marshall *RESTRICTED*, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - PA 0952-0955 Phillips *RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - PA 0956-0957 Gwynn*RESTRICTED*, 1996; undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - PA 0960 Washington *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - PA 0964 Eckles *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - PA 0968-0969 Lightner *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - PA 0972-0974 Marinelli *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - PA 0980-0983 Gease *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997; undated (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
    - PA 0984-0987 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - PA 0985-0986 Bailey *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - PA 0988-0991 Smith *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
    - PA 0996-0999 Brown*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - PA 4000-4001,4005 Bolden *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - PA 4002,PA 0826 Spotz*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - SC 1201-1204 Davis *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - SC 1205-1208 Charping *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - SC 1209-1212 Sims*RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - SC 1213 Longworth *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 15 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - SC 1214 Longworth *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 15 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - SC 1215 Longworth *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 15 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - SC 1216 Longworth *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 15 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - SC 1217-1220 Manning *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - SC 1221-1224 Davis *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - SC 1225-1229 Southerland *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
    - SC 1230-1233 Smith *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - SC 1238-SC 1241 Green *RESTRICTED*, 1992 September 15 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - SC 1242-1245 Davis *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - SC 1246-1249 Van Dohlen *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - SC 1250-1253 Hoffman *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - SC 1258 Rocheville *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - SC 1259 Rocheville *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - SC 1260 Rocheville*RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - SC 1261 Rocheville *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - SC 1262 Hunter*RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - SC 1263 Hunter *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - SC 1264 Hunter*RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - SC 1265 Hunter *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - SC 1266-1268 Carn *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - SC 1270-1272 Young *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - SC 1274-1276 Torrence*RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - SC 1278-1279 Hall *RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - SC 1282 Cooper *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - SC 1283 Cooper *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - SC 1286 Bell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - SC 1287 Bell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - SC 1288 Bell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - SC 1289 Bell *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - SC 1290-1293 Wodke*RESTRICTED*, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
    - SC 1294 Torrence *RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - SC 1295 Torrence*RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - SC 1296 Torrence*RESTRICTED*, 1992 October 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - SC 1298 Allen *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - SC 1302-1305 McGraw*RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - SC 1306-1309 Buiton *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - SC 1310-1313 Brooks *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - SC 1314-1317 Cross *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - SC 1318 Middleton *RESTRICTED*, 1993 February 8 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - SC 1319 Middleton *RESTRICTED*, 1994 February 8 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - SC 1320 Middleton *RESTRICTED*, 1995 February 8 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - SC 1321 Middleton *RESTRICTED*, 1996 February 8 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - SC 1322-1325 Pierce *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - TX 1501-1504 Penry *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
    - TX 1505-1508 Davis*RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - TX 1509-1510 Nilson *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - TX 1513-1514 Dunn *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - TX 1517-1518 Rousseau *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - TX 1521-1523 Proctor *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - TX 1525-1527 Napier *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - TX 1529-1531 Butler *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - TX 1533-1534 Johnson*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - tX 1537-1540 Miniel *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - TX 1541 Beltland*RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - TX 1547 Marks *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - TX 1549-1552 Peterman *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - TX 1553-1556 Jones *RESTRICTED*, 1995; undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - TX 1557-1558 Rabboni *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - TX 1561-1563 Barzar *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - TX 1565-1566 Nelson *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - TX 1569-1570 Smith*RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - TX 1581-1584 Curry *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
    - TX 1585-1588,1646 Powell *RESTRICTED*, 1995; 1997 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - TX 1585-1588,1646 Powell *RESTRICTED*, 1995; 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - TX 1589-1592 Rios *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
    - TX 1593-1596 Cordova *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - TX 1597-1600 Moreno *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5-6)
    - TX 1601-1607 Lockhart *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - TX 1601-1602 Lockhart *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - TX 1605-1607 Richardson *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
    - TX 1609-1612 Green*RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
    - TX 1617 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, 1995 August 24 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - TX 1618 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, 1995 August 24 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - TX 1619 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - TX 1620 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - TX 1621 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, 1997 July 31 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - TX 1613-1616,1647-1648 Satterwhite *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - TX 1613-1616, 1647-1648 Satterwhite *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - TX 1617 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - TX 1618 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - TX 1619 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - TX 1620-1621 Cruz *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - TX 1617-1621 Oliver David Cruz case overview *RESTRICTED*, 2001 December 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - TX 5000-5001 Floyd. Jr. *RESTRICTED*, 1999; undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - TX 5002-5004 Rodarte *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
    - TX 5005-5007 Resendez *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
    - TX 5008-5010 Villegas*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - TX 5011-5012 Moreno *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - TX 5014-5018 Cisneros*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
    - TN 2000-2003 Smith *RESTRICTED*, 1997; undated (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
    - TN 2004-2005 Burns *RESTRICTED*, 1999; 2003 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - TN 2004-2005 Burns *RESTRICTED*, 1999; 2003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - TN 2006-2008 Keough*RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - TN 2009-2015 Johnson *RESTRICTED*, 1997; undated (Box 28, Folder 3-6)
    - TN 2016-2018 Hathaway*RESTRICTED*, 1997; undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - TN 2019-2022 Godsey *RESTRICTED*, 1999; undated (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
    - TN 2024-2025 Carter *RESTRICTED*, 1999; undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - TN 2026-2029 Williams *RESTRICTED*, 1998-1999; undated (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
    - TN 2030 Cribbs *RESTRICTED*, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - TN 2034-2036 Brown *RESTRICTED*, 1999; undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - TN 2034-2049 Bigbee *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992; 1999 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - TN 2040-2042 Beckham *RESTRICTED*, 1994; 1999 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - Tn2043-2046 Summarall *restricted*, 1994; 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - TN 2047-2048 Hale *RESTRICTED*, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - TN 2049 dunn *RESTRICTED*, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - TN 2050-2052 Nicholo *RESTRICTED*, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - VA 1651-1653 Rea *RESTRICTED*, 1991; undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - VA 1655-1659 Copeland *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
    - VA 1660-1664 Hamlin *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - VA 1669-1674 Moran *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 11-12)
    - VA 1675-1678 Whitt *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - VA 1683 Rogers*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - VA 1687-1690 Satcher*RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - VA 1691-1693 Fox *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - VA 1695-1700 Wright *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 3-4)
    - VA 1701-1702 Weeks *RESTRICTED*, 1996; undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - (State not listed) Def Id 1606 Sanchez *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Administrative, 1990-2001; 1.2; 1
    This series is arranged alphabetically.
    This series includes the administrative materials from the first phase of the CJP. It includes codebooks to the juror instruments, grant materials, and correspondence.
    - Additional Question for North Carolina Jurors, *Restricted*, 1991 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Blank Juror Interview Instrument, 1995 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Capital Jury Project Interviewer's Guide, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Codebooks IIA Elements Coding Instrument, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Coded Juror Instruments, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Coded Juror Instruments, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Coded Juror Instrument, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Elements Coding Instrument, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Coded Juror Instruments, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Coded Juror Instruments, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Coding Catalog XLS, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Complete Set of memos, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Crime Code Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Exercise of Discretion by Capital Jurors, NSF 90-13252, Related Correspondence, 1991; 1993; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Blank Juror Interview Instrument, 1995 June 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Grant Proposal for CJP I to NSF, 1990 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
    - Nebraska Criminal Homicide Review Project Data Collection Instrument, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Proportionality Review Study, 1997 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Response Set Answer Cards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Resums, 1991-2001; 2003; 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Tennessee Capital Jury Project Jonathan Wesley Stephenson Case Information Sheet, *Restricted*, 1992 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Tennessee Capital Jury Project Case Information Sheet, *Restricted*, 1992 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Tennessee Capital Jury Project Case Information Sheet, *Restricted*, 1992 June 23 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - William Bowers Correspondence with Marla Sandys, 1999 May 4; 2000 February 6; 2001 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - William Bowers CJP I Tentative Book Outline, 2001 June 26 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Audiotapes of Juror Interviews, 1990-2004; 1.3
    This series contains the audio interviews of jurors conducted in CJP I. Many cassettes contain more than one interview from the same state. The cassettes and micro cassettes are arranged by state and juror interview number. The audiotapes are restricted materials and all reproductions are prohibited.
    - AL 1801, AL 1809, AL 1811, AL 1814, AL 1830*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 1)
    - AL 1805, AL 1828*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 2)
    - AL 1827*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 3)
    - AL 1832*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 4)
    - AL 1833*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 5)
    - AL1836, AL 1815*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 6)
    - AL 1840, AL 1829*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 7)
    - AL 1845, AL 1870*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 8)
    - AL 1847*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 9)
    - AL 1848, AL 1847*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 10)
    - AL 1853*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 11)
    - AL 1873 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 12)
    - AL 1881*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 13)
    - CA 0001*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 14)
    - CA 0001*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 15)
    - CA 0002*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 16)
    - CA 0002*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 17)
    - CA 0003*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 18)
    - CA 0003 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 19)
    - CA 0003 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 20)
    - CA 0004*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 21)
    - CA 0004*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 22)
    - CA 0005*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 23)
    - CA 0005*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 24)
    - CA 0005*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 25)
    - CA 0007*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 26)
    - CA 0007*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 27)
    - CA 0007*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 28)
    - CA 0007*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 29)
    - CA 0008*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 30)
    - CA 0008*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 31)
    - CA 0008*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 32)
    - CA 0013 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 33)
    - CA 0014*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 34)
    - CA 0014*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 35)
    - CA 0015*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 36)
    - CA 0015*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 37)
    - CA 0016*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 38)
    - CA 0016*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 39)
    - CA 0018*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 40)
    - CA 0018*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 41)
    - CA 0018*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 42)
    - CA 0019*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 43)
    - CA 0019*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 44)
    - CA 0019*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 45)
    - CA 0019*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 46)
    - CA 0021 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 47)
    - CA 0021 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 48)
    - CA 0021*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 49)
    - CA 0021 *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 50)
    - CA 0023*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 51)
    - CA 0023*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 52)
    - CA 0023*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 53)
    - CA 0024*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 54)
    - CA 0024*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 55)
    - CA 0024*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 56)
    - CA 0026*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 57)
    - CA 0026*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 58)
    - CA 0027*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 59)
    - CA 0027*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 60)
    - CA 0029*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 61)
    - CA 0030*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 62)
    - CA 0030*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 63)
    - CA 0030*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 64)
    - CA 0031*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 65)
    - CA 0031*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 66)
    - CA 0031*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 67)
    - CA 0032*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 68)
    - CA 0032*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 69)
    - CA 0032*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 70)
    - CA 0039*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 71)
    - CA 0041*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 72)
    - CA 0041*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 73)
    - CA 0041*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 74)
    - CA 0042*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 75)
    - CA 0042*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 76)
    - CA 0042*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 77)
    - CA 0043*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 78)
    - CA 0044*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 79)
    - CA 0044*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 80)
    - CA 0047*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 81)
    - CA 0047*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 82)
    - CA 0047*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 83)
    - CA 0049*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 84)
    - CA 0049*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 85)
    - CA 0052*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 86)
    - CA 0052*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 87)
    - CA 0052*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 88)
    - CA 0053*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 89)
    - CA 0053*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 90)
    - CA 0053*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 91)
    - CA 0054*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 92)
    - CA 0054*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 93)
    - CA 0054*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 94)
    - CA 0055*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 95)
    - CA 0055*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 96)
    - CA 0055*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 97)
    - CA 0056*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 98)
    - CA 0056*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 99)
    - CA 0057*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 100)
    - CA 0057*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 101)
    - CA 0059*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 102)
    - CA 0059*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 103)
    - CA 0059*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 104)
    - CA 0059*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 105)
    - CA 0060*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 106)
    - CA 0060*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 107)
    - CA 0061*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 108)
    - CA 0061*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 109)
    - CA 0061*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 110)
    - CA 0062*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 111)
    - CA 0062*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 112)
    - CA 0063*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 113)
    - CA 0063*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 114)
    - CA 0063*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 115)
    - CA 0064*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 116)
    - CA 0064*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 117)
    - CA 0064*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 118)
    - CA 0065*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 119)
    - CA 0065*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 120)
    - CA 0066*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 121)
    - CA 0066*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 122)
    - CA 0066*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 123)
    - CA 0067*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 124)
    - CA 0067*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 125)
    - CA 0067*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 126)
    - CA 0068*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 127)
    - CA 0068*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 128)
    - CA 0070*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 129)
    - CA 0070*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 130)
    - CA 0072*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 131)
    - CA 0072*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 132)
    - CA 0073*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 133)
    - CA 0073*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 134)
    - CA 0074*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 135)
    - CA 0074*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 136)
    - CA 0075*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 137)
    - CA 0075*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 138)
    - CA 0076*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 139)
    - CA 0076*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 140)
    - CA 0077*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 141)
    - CA 0077*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 142)
    - CA 0077*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 143)
    - CA 0078*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 144)
    - CA 0078*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 145)
    - CA 0078*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 146)
    - CA 0079*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 147)
    - CA 0079*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 148)
    - CA 0080*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 149)
    - CA 0080*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 150)
    - CA 0083*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 151)
    - CA 0083*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 152)
    - CA 0084*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 153)
    - CA 0084*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 154)
    - CA 0084*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Cassette 155)
    - CA 0085*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 156)
    - CA 0085*RESTRICTED*, Undated (Mini-dv 157)